<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Old School Football Coach</title>
    <link>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Old School Football Coach</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 20:50:49 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Build 21-06 Available</title>
      <link>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/build-2106/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 20:03:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/build-2106/</guid>
      <description>Happy Memorial Day! A new development build (21-06) of Old School Football Coach is now publicly available, which, in addition to various bug fixes, includes 2 major features!
Player Fatigue The football players on your team have always had a stamina attribute, but until now it didn&amp;rsquo;t have a major impact on their performance. That all changes with this update. Players will now get fatigued as they play, and as their condition worsens so will their other abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build 21-05 Available</title>
      <link>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/build-2105/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 19:46:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/build-2105/</guid>
      <description>Development build (21-05) of Old School Football Coach is now publicly available! Notable changes include:
New Features / Improvements  In career mode, recruits can now have a new interest: &amp;ldquo;Recent Success&amp;rdquo;. In other words, if recent success is important to a recruit, you can influence them more towards your team if you&amp;rsquo;ve been doing well lately. This interest is also different from the other ones because the recruit&amp;rsquo;s feelings can change on it week-to-week depending on how your team is doing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build 21-05 Available</title>
      <link>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/build-202104-now-available/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 14:55:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/build-202104-now-available/</guid>
      <description>A new early access development build (2021-04) of Old School Football Coach is now publicly available! Notable changes include:
Postseason Games There is now support for postseason games and they are highly customizable! You can configure the number of playoff spots available in your league and decide of if only the top-ranked teams make it in, or if conference champions have an automatic bid. You can also decide if you want to create your own bowl games and how teams get selected for them as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old School Football Coach Dev Build 2021-02 Now Available</title>
      <link>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/oldschoolfbcoach-dev-build-202102-now-available/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 21:06:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/oldschoolfbcoach-dev-build-202102-now-available/</guid>
      <description>Another new development build of Old School Football Coach is publicly available! Notable changes include:
New Features  Conference championship games have been implemented in career mode. At the end of the regular season the top two teams in each conference will be matched up for a conference championship game. It is now possible to edit conferences in the League Management menu in addition to creating and deleting them. Penalties can now be declined.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Old School Football Coach Dev Build 2021-01 Now Available</title>
      <link>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/oldschoolfbcoach-dev-build-202101-now-available/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 21:28:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/oldschoolfbcoach-dev-build-202101-now-available/</guid>
      <description>A new development build of Old School Football Coach is now publicly available! This update largely focuses on new features and improvements, listed below.
Remappable Keybindings It&amp;rsquo;s now possible to configure in-game controls from the Settings menu. Right now this only supports keyboard keys, but controller support is a planned feature for the future.
Control the Snap While on offense and using the standard control method, it is now possible to control when the ball gets snapped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Early Access Available on itch.io</title>
      <link>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/early-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 22:08:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/early-access/</guid>
      <description>Old School Football Coach is now available for early access on itch.io! The game is very playable in it&amp;rsquo;s current state, but I&amp;rsquo;ll be continuing development and delivering additional features and improvements in the future. Those who purchase the early access will be supporting development and will receive updates at no additional charge!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Launch</title>
      <link>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/website-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2020 12:48:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://OldSchoolFBCoach.github.io/blog/website-launch/</guid>
      <description>This is the new website for Old School Football Coach! Old School Football Coach is an in-development American college football PC game in the sports management simulation genre. You can call your team&amp;rsquo;s plays and do your best to lead them to victory. For a more in-depth experience, the game also offers a career mode where you can recruit new players, set up depth charts, and other activities you would expect from a college football coach.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
